grapheffect.com 2014-12-25

# SHIFT | Privacy

Version 1.0

Last Revised: November 30. 2012

Welcome to Shift.com, a website operated by GraphEffect, Inc. d/b/a SHIFT (“SHIFT”, “We” or “Us”) (the “Website“), and the home of the SHIFT collaboration platform that connects people across and within organizations to help them work more efficiently (the “SHIFT Service”).

This Privacy Policy governs your interactions with the Website and the SHIFT Service and any additional services provided by SHIFT made available through the Website (collectively, the “Services“). The Services include applications that are integrated with and accessed from the SHIFT Service and published by SHIFT (the “SHIFT Integrated Applications“), for example, our GraphEffect media execution platform application. This Privacy Policy does not govern your interactions with third party applications that integrate with the SHIFT Service (“Third Party Integrated Applications” or “TPIA“). Please see the section below on TPIAs for more information.

Capitalized words in this Privacy Policy that are not defined here have the meaning given to them in the SHIFT Terms of Service made available at[www.shift.com/tos](http://www.shift.com/tos).

A Note to Users Outside of the United States. Your Personal Information may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By using the Services, you are authorizing the transfer of your Personal Information in this way.

Types of Information. “Personal Information” means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing information. “Anonymous Information” means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Information and Anonymous Information, as described below.

Information We Collect.

Information You Provide. We collect Personal Information when you knowingly provide it to us, including in the following ways:

We may collect Personal Information from you, such as your first and last name, company information, e-mail and password when you create an account to use the SHIFT Service (“Account”);

When using the Services, you will submit Personal Information, for example, the individuals you invite to join a team, files you upload into a team area or postings you make to a public area of the Website or Services;

We will collect information about the Integrated Applications you access through the Services as provided below in the section entitled Information Collected via Technology. We may collect Personal Information through a TPIA, with the understanding that a publisher of a TPIA is contractually required to disclose what Personal Information it is disclosing to us in the its TPIA privacy policy. Please see the section below on TPIAs for more information about how we interact with TPIAs;

If you engage in any purchases through the Services, we will collect all information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card information, billing information and shipping information (collectively “Billing Information”);

We collect feedback on products and services if you provide it;

We collect the information you provide when you participate in one of our surveys, and

If you contact us regarding support for the Services, we may collect other types of Personal Information that you provide to us voluntarily, such as your operating system and location.

Information Collected via Technology.

To make our Services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you automatically, including your browser type, operating system and Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session);

We also automatically collect information about the Integrated Applications you access through the Services, including information about how, when and for how long, and

We also use cookies and URL information to gather and store information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and which you viewed. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s browser while you are viewing a web site. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can learn more about cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.com.

Information Collected from You About Others. If you decide to invite a third party to create an Account or join a Team, we will collect your and the third party’s names and e-mail addresses in order to send an e-mail and follow up with the third party.

Information Collected from Social Networking Sites. If you log on to the Service with your login credentials from a social network site (“SNS”) (e.g., through Facebook Connect), we may receive Personal Information about you from such SNS in accordance with its terms of use and privacy policy and your privacy settings on such SNS. For example, if your Facebook privacy settings allow, Facebook may share your friend list with us, in order to help us establish your Account and find other Service users that you know. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via the Service.

Use of Your Personal Information

General Use. In general, we use your Personal Information as necessary for us to provide the Services, respond to requests that you make or to aid us in serving you better, including in the following specific ways:

to facilitate the creation of, and secure, your Account on our network;

identify you as a User in our system;

provide the Services you request;

improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Services;

send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your Account was created;

send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories, and to call you on the telephone for the same purposes;

respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests, and

to send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to our Services, those of trusted partners and for other marketing purposes.

Notwithstanding the above, we use your Billing Information solely to process your order and for no other purpose.

Creation of Anonymous Information. We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name or email address) that make the information personally identifiable to you. We reserve the right to use this Anonymous Information without restriction including to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Services and improve navigation.

Disclosure of Your Personal Information. We disclose your Personal Information as described below and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

As You Direct. We will share your Personal Information with third parties if you ask us to do so. For example, files that you post in any team area will be available to other members of the team and if you invite someone to be a member of the team, we will provide the invitee any information contained in your invitation.

Our Vendors. We may share your Personal Information with third party service providers who work on our behalf including for the following reasons: to provide you with the Services that we offer you through our Website; to conduct quality assurance testing; to facilitate creation of accounts; to provide technical support; to process payments and/or to provide other services to SHIFT. As a general rule, these third party service providers are required not to use your Personal Information other than to provide the services requested by SHIFT or in some aggregated or anonymous manner.

Affiliates, Acquisitions, Bankruptcy. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (“Affiliates“), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, your Personal Information may also be transferred on a standalone basis.

Other Disclosures. Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Information (as described below), SHIFT may disclose Personal Information if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (i) in connection with any legal investigation; (ii) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on SHIFT; (iii) to protect or defend the rights or property of SHIFT or users of the Services; and/or (iv) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or Terms of Use.

Third Party Integrated Applications.

Framing TPIA Content. One of the many features of the SHIFT Service is that other applications can integrate with the SHIFT Service and the power of collaboration is felt exponentially. When you view a TPIA through the SHIFT Service you do so through a “frame”. The TPIA pages and content you see through the frame are in fact sitting on the servers controlled by the TPIA publisher, not us. So, unless you copy and paste (or, if the TPIA allows, otherwise import) the content into the Shift Service, we will not have access to, or store, the TPIA content viewed through the frame. Similarly, unless you expressly authorize us, we do not provide your Personal Information to any TPIA publisher.

Authentication. We have created interfaces that allow you to connect with a TPIA, and authorize us to access and display your TPIA account. In order to provide this authorization, you do not provide us with your TPIA user name or password, but you will log-in to the TPIA directly through our Service. Once authorized by you, the TPIA provides us a token that allows the TPIA to recognize us when we ask, on your behalf, for access to your account information or to post information. To be clear, we cannot, and will not, access your TPIA account with this token unless you expressly authorize us to do so in each case.

TPIA Privacy. We are bound by this SHIFT privacy policy and the publisher of the TPIA is bound by its own privacy policy. Each publisher of a TPIA is contractually required by SHIFT to host and make available to you a statement of privacy practices that discloses its information collection, use and sharing practices (a “TPIA Privacy Statement”), including what Personal Information, if any, it provides to us. The TPIA Privacy Statement, and not the SHIFT privacy policy, governs the third party’s use of your personal informational. We are not bound by any TPIA Privacy Policy.

Supplemental Privacy Provisions. Specific Services, including SHIFT Integrated Applications, may have information collection, use and sharing disclosures that are specific to the Service (“Supplemental Privacy Provisions”). Any Supplemental Privacy Provisions will either be listed in this Agreement or will be presented to you for your acceptance when you sign up to use the Service. If any provision in this Privacy Policy is inconsistent with any provision in the Supplemental Privacy Provisions, the Supplemental Privacy Provisions will control, but only for such Service.

Third Party Websites. When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Website and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Information or Anonymous Information from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of information after you click on links to such outside websites.

A Note About Children. We do not intentionally gather Personal Information from visitors who are under the age of 13.

Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

Choices. We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information.

We will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our Services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below).

Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service related communication, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

Changes to Personal Information. You may change any of your Personal Information in your Account by editing your Account settings or by sending an e-mail to us at [privacy@shift.com.](mailto:privacy@shift.com) You may request deletion of your Personal Information by us, but please note that we may be required to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. We may retain your information for fraud or similar purposes.

Security of Your Personal Information. SHIFT is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We also require you to enter a password to access your Account information. Please do not disclose your Account password to unauthorized people. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while SHIFT uses reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information, SHIFT cannot guarantee its security.

Contact Information. SHIFT welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please e-mail us at [privacy@shift.com](mailto:privacy@shift.com) to share your thoughts or questions.

Changes to This Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Website. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Website. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Service. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your Account with us. Continued use of our Website or Service following notice of such changes will indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
